http://www.myvisionboard.com/privacy.php

Privacy Policy
Thank you for using Vision Board! We wrote this policy to help you understand what information we collect, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding your information. Because we're an Internet company, some of the concepts below are a little technical, but we've tried our best to explain things in a simple and clear way. We welcome your questions and comments on this policy.
What information do we collect?
We collect information in two ways:
1. When you give it to us or give us permission to obtain it.
When you sign up for or use our products, you voluntarily give us certain information. This can include your name, profile photo, posts, comments, likes, email address you used to sign up, and any other information you provide us. If you're using Vision Board on your mobile device, you can also choose to provide us with location data.
You also may give us permission to access your information in other services. For example, you may link your Facebook or Twitter account to Vision Board, which allows us to obtain information from those accounts (e.g., your friends or contacts). The information we obtain from those services often depends on your settings or their privacy policies, so be sure to check what those are.
2. We get technical information when you use our products.
These days, whenever you use a website, mobile application, or other Internet service, there's certain information that almost always gets created and recorded in an automated way. The same is true when you use our products, and here are some of the types of information we collect in this way.
Log Data. When you use Vision Board, our servers automatically record information about your interaction with our products ("log data"), including information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website or your mobile app sends when you use it to access Vision Board. This log data may include your Internet Protocol address, the address of the web page you were visiting before you came to Vision Board, browser type and settings, the date and time of your request, and how you used Vision Board.
Depending on how you're accessing our products, we may use "cookies" (a small text file sent by your computer each time you visit our website, unique to your Vision Board account or your browser), or similar technologies to record log data. When we use cookies, we may use "session" cookies (that last until you close your browser) or "persistent" cookies (that last until you or your browser delete them). For example, we may use cookies to store your language preferences or other Vision Board settings so you don't have to set them up every time you visit Vision Board.
Device Information. In addition to log data, we may also collect information about the device you're using Vision Board on, including what type of device it is, what operating system you're using, device settings, unique device identifiers, and crash data. Whether we collect some or all of this information often depends on what type of device you're using and its settings. For example, different types of information are available depending on whether you're using a Mac or a PC, or an iPhone or an Android phone. To learn more about what information your device makes available to us, please also check the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider.
How do we use the information we collect?
We use the information we collect to provide our products to you and make them better, develop new products, and protect Vision Board and our users. For example, we may log how often people use two different versions of a product, which can help us understand which version is better.
We also use the information we collect to offer you customized content -- including helping you discover posts or boards you might like or provide you with tailored advertising. For example, if you've indicated that you're interested in cooking, we may suggest food-related posts, boards, or people.
We also use the information we collect to:
send you updates (such as when certain activity, like repost or comments, happens on Vision Board), newsletters, marketing materials and other information that may be of interest to you. For example, depending on your email notification settings, we may send you weekly updates that include posts you may like. You can decide to stop getting these updates by updating your account settings (or through other settings we may provide).
Respond to your questions or comments.
The information we collect may be "personally identifiable" (meaning it can be used to specifically identify you as a unique person) or "non-personally identifiable" (meaning it can't be used to specifically identify you). We use both types of information, and combinations of both types, as described above. We may use or store information wherever Vision Board does business, including countries outside your own.
What choices do you have about your information?
Our goal is to give you simple and meaningful choices over your information. If you have a Vision Board account, many of the choices you have on Vision Board are built directly in to the product or your account settings. For example, you can:
Access and change information in your profile page at any time.
Link or unlink your Vision Board account from an account on another service (e.g., Facebook or Twitter). For some services (like Facebook), you can also choose whether or not to publish your activity on Vision Board to that service.
Create or be added to a secret board. Secret boards are visible to you and other participants in the board, and any participant may choose to make the contents of the board available to anyone else. For example, another participant may invite someone else to the board, make the board available to an app they use to view Vision Board, or even just take an image from the board and email it to their friends. For more information about secret boards, please visit our Help Center.
Close your account at any time. When you close your account, we'll deactivate it and remove your posts and boards from Vision Board. We may retain archived copies of your information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes (including to help address fraud and spam).
In addition to the examples above, we offer other choices that you can learn more about in our Help Center.
You may have choices available to you through the device or software you use to access Vision Board. For example:
The browser you use may provide you with the ability to control cookies or other types of local data storage;
Your mobile device may provide you with choices around how and whether location or other data is shared with us.
To learn more about these choices, please see the information provided by the device or software provider.
What information do we collect?
Vision Board is a tool people use to find their inspirations, make them a reality, and inspire others in the process. When you create public boards and posts, anyone can view them. You may also provide us with profile page information that that anyone can view. The other limited instances where we may share your personal information include&colon
When we have your consent. This includes sharing information with other services (like Facebook or Twitter) when you’ve chosen to link to your Vision Board account to those services or publish your activity on Vision Board to them. For example, you can choose to publish your posts to Facebook or Twitter.
We may employ third party companies or individuals to process personal information on our behalf based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy. For example, we may share data with a security consultant to help us get better at identifying spam or with our accountants to make sure we’re keeping the books right. In addition, some of the information we request may be collected by third party providers on our behalf. For more information about the providers we use, please see our Help Center.
If we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety, rights, or property of the public, any person, or Vision Board; or to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
We may engage in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, or similar transaction or proceeding that involves the transfer of the information described in this Policy.
We may also share aggregated or non-personally identifiable information with our partners or others. For example, we may tell a business using Vision Board how many people reposted something they shared, or the percentage of people who click a on post after viewing it.
Our Policy on Children’s Information
Vision Board is not directed to children under 13. If you learn that your minor child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us.
How do we make changes to this policy?
We may change this policy from time to time, and if we do we’ll post any changes on this page. If you continue to use Vision Board after those changes are in effect, you agree to the revised policy. If the changes are significant, we may provide more prominent notice or obtain your consent as required by law.
Home |
About The App |
Contact Us |
Login
Privacy Policy |
Terms of Service
Copyright © 2020 Self Esteem Seminars, L.P. All Rights Reserved. Jack Canfield™ is a trademark of Self Esteem Seminars, L.P. &
Copyright © 2020 Mogulworx LLC.
